

CONTACT INFORMATION

(063) 135-35-52 petrozabila@gmail.com LinkedIn GitHub Cherkasy, Ukraine

TECH SKILL

- HTML5/CSS3/SASS
- Responsive/Adaptive design
- GIT
- JavaScript
- React
- Redux
- REST API
- Webpack
- Parcel
- Node.js

SOFT SKILLS

Growth Mindset
Teamwork
Creativity
Good communication

LANGUAGES

Englich - Upper-Intermediate Ukrainian - Native Russian - Native Farsi - Intermediate

PETRO ZABILA

FRONT-FND DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

Junior Front-End developer.

I have reasonable knowledge of HTML, CSS, JavaScript ad REACT a well as practical experience in keeping my workflow in accordance with Agile/SCRUM methodology while working in a team.

Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as a part of a team.

I am a fast-learner, responsible and ready for challenging tasks.

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

• ICECREAM-GALAXY, Link (HTML, SASS, Parcel)

A wesite with responsive layout. Role: developer.

 <u>FILMOTEKA</u>, <u>Link</u> (HTML, SASS, JS, Handlebars, REST API, AJAX, Parcel)

Application for searching movies and reviewing its content. Role: developer.

- <u>CONTACT BOOK</u>, <u>Link (REACT</u>, REDUX, Axios, Styled Components) Application for adding and managing contacts in a user's personal contactbook. Role: developer.
- PETLY, <u>Link</u> (REACT, REDUX, Axios, Styled Components, Node.js) Application where you can add, find, sell pets. Role: developer.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Journalist

Deartment of Education and Science of Cherkasy State Administration | 2013-2022

- · website content management
- news coverage
- writing reports on education and science themes
- · photoshop design

Sales manager

ASM Trading | 2010-2013

- website content management
- · negotiation with counteragents
- · interpretation while negotiations
- · sales market researches

EDUCATION

IT School GoIT

2021 - 2022

Front-End Full-Stack Developer

Kyiv National Aviation University

2010 - 2013

Specialist's degree in Economic Law

Kyiv National Linguistic University

2005 - 2010

Master's degree in translation of Farsi and English languages